Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching.
The answer I've been looking for. The dream I've been longing for.
The moment I got it, something just popped.
I thought I knew this day would come.
Goodbye. I can't let the sound of that shatter my fragile heart.
We're as fragile as glass, and we'll keep on connecting.
I remember the time when we believed in each other.
I remember.
We looked up at the same sky, we shared the same wind.
We've shared smiles, we've shared pain.
And now there's a light shining on each of our paths.
♪ It's time to go, tears are in the air
I'll wave to you, I'll wave to you
Thank you, hello, goodbye
From the bottom of my heart
I'm Kisora Niinuma, a 15-year-old high school freshman from Aichi, Japan, and a member of the Tsubaki Factory.
Recently, I have been addicted to eating nata de coco.
What do you like about nata de coco?
I really like the fact that the texture is a bit crunchy.
There was a time when I liked it too.
You are dressed like a nata de coco.
Yes, I do.
Thank you for watching.
Hello! Stay, this time with Kisura Niinuma and Ami Tanimoto from Tsubaki Factory!
These two will be presenting this time, so please stay with us until the end.
This will be my last show before my graduation. Sta. MC before her graduation.
I started with the video of my first MC.
My first MC was recorded with Mayumi Yajima of Cute and
Mayumi Yajima and Ami.
Do you remember that?
No, I didn't.
But I remember it so well.
I was so nervous just to do this MC job.
I was so nervous just to do this, but I remembered that Mr. Yajima, who was a senior of mine, was there.
When he introduced himself at the beginning, he said he was addicted to nata de coco.
Ui Ui felt it too. Wow Ui Ui felt it too.
In fact, I do.
But when I thought that the first MC was with Ami and the last MC was also with Ami
I was very deeply moved.
Thank you so much!
You're so nice!
We Tsubaki Factory will release our 12th single on August 28th!
It's a triple A-side single, including a new song, Baby Spider Seishun Exabyte!
Yes.
yes
original
og
this was not June
This is also Nippon Budokan remember
I love you
This is possession burial
Here you go.
I've got one more book.
You know, I'm going to be watching a video of you sois...
Are you ready to have some fun?
Yeah!
That didn't take forever.
I'm nervous.
Are you ready to have some fun?Are you ready to have some fun?
I am!
Yes, this will be the first and last time
Let's have fun at the Budokan!
I'll do my best!
Thank you very much for your time!
Thank you for your hard work!
Keep smiling, keep on smiling, keep on giving me something to smile about.
Keep smiling, just like the old days.
You're so sweet.
You're so sweet and you're so precious
My heart aches
But I'm going slowly I'm going slowly
I wonder if you can draw me
Get down I'm going backwards I'm going slowly
The future waits for me there
The future's waiting for me.
I love this place. You guys love this place.
I'm having fun I'm laughing I'm having a good day
I'm stuck in the blur, the blur, the blur, the blur, protect it
Be brave, speak up, judge it all
It's all stupid
I'm the one who won't
Ah, I can't do this anymore
I can't open my heart
I'm so bad at this
The code is the leader.
Leader.
Come on, we'll walk, we'll walk
I'll walk, I'll walk, I'll walk
We'll walk, we'll walk, we'll walk
Stage.
Scold me, Tanaka, scold me some more, like we're family
You're too big, you're too cool
You're too cool... my heart aches... keep it up. My heart aches, keep it up and give it to me
Tears well up Get down
Anywhere I go, I go
I'll go anywhere, I'll go
I'll go to the future I'll go to the light
I go to the future
I'm going to the now
Thank you. I want the rest.
Without me, it's so funny. The good times, the good days.
I'm actually afraid of the pages going crazy.
I'm actually scared that the pages are going to go haywire I'm actually scared that they're going to go haywire
I know it's all there.
I'm the one who's cheating.
Ah, I can't, I can't, I can't
I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it, I can't do it
Count to easy
I want to roll
It's time
Mooty, Mooty, Mooty
Now's the time Breaking my heart
Count to three
Get down
I love you for trying so hard
Tsubaki Factory's Mission Maki Sora and
and Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory.
I'd like to talk a little about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so please answer them without thinking too much.
Let's get started.
Today is June 5th, Rakugo day.
Mispronunciation
What is your favorite beauty product right now?
Head massage machine
It's been 4 months since a new member joined Tsubaki Factory.
What changes have you seen in Tsubaki Factory?
We have become younger.
Which Hello Project song would you like to sing in spring? Haru renga What Hello Project songs would you like to sing in spring? Haru renga
Tsubaki Factory has entered its 10th year since its formation. What are your goals for the 10th anniversary?
To let as many people as possible know about us.
What made you laugh out loud recently?
What did I say wrong?
It's not me, it's my mom.
One day, me, my mom, and my dog were going out to eat at a restaurant.
When my mom called me to make a reservation
She asked for one dog and two dogs.
She said we were turned into animals too.
That made me laugh.
Ami's mom is funny, isn't she?
She talks a lot, which I love.
And Tsubaki Factory is now in its 10th year.
What did Ami-chan say?
You know...
Our goal is to get as many people as possible to know about us.
This has always been our goal.
We would like to be known by many people in Japan
And also to people all over the world.
I want more and more people to know about Tsubaki Factory
I hope that more and more people will come to know and love Tsubaki Factory.
Questions for Kisora will be asked after the VTR.
Haloste
Journalism calendar
Just a nice character
Bang Eles if you want to show them off
If you commit a crime, it's a bros
Seats are also padded.
Angulum Bilital Ichigeki June 12 ON SAIYO
Rumor of Narcissi Whoever it is, whatever it is, I love my self
Anjelm Rumor of Narcissi June 12 ON SAIYO
Morning Musume。24コンサートツアー春 もっとモーニング娘。 The finals are over!
It was so much fun to be able to visit the audience at various places.
I ran and sweated a lot, and I got to say how cute the pandas are.
I felt even more passionate today!
Every time I made eye contact with the members, everyone was so passionate.
I could feel that they were having a great time together as one. I could feel the sense of togetherness and enjoyment in the show, and it was a very enjoyable show.
It was a very enjoyable concert. Thank you very much!
And, you know, I performed for the first time at this show.
The song from the new single “Somewhat Sentimental
It is the most powerful and fascinating single.
It will be released on August 14!
How did you like it? First performance
The song of a somewhat sentimental time... you must have been surprised, right? I thought so.
That's right.
When we heard it for the first time, we were like, “Is this a song? We were like...
We were so surprised.
We wanted to see the expressions on the fans' faces, but we also wanted to be in the world of the song.
When we finished the song, you could hear a little buzz in the audience.
I thought, “No, this is the right song! I thought, “This was the right one!
I'm going to keep doing my best to make the audience love it more and more.
I want to do my best so that people will love it more and more.
And the strongest is the one that made me sing it, thinking that I am the strongest.
And the first fake part?
I was so happy!
What happened?
We were all excited from that point on, and I thought we were able to perform the songs with a lot of excitement.
Please look forward to both songs in the new single. Thank you very much.
That was TUKO from Morning Stage.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Kisora-chan.
Yes, sir.
Tsubaki Factory Shinnuma Kisora photo book Kisora was released last month.
If I were to describe this photo book in one word, it would be
I am 24 years old
The first performance by the 12 members on the spring tour
The perfect word for the current 12 members is
Fresh
Where would you like to go now?
Overseas
My favorite thing about Ami Tanimoto is
Her kindness
What would you like to tell us about your last Halo! Please tell us what you want to tell us now.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
thank you very much.
I don't know.
Where would you like to go abroad?
I don't really have a specific place in mind.
Last month I went to Shanghai with Tsubaki Factory to do a live concert.
Since last year, I've been fortunate enough to have a lot of overseas gigs.
I felt that the world is a big place, so I want to go to many places abroad.
I said “overseas” because I want to visit many places.
Then, what do you like about me?
No way!
That's true, but Ami-chan...
I'm sure you'd say the same thing if I asked any of the members.
I feel that you're really kind.
That's...
I don't know.
It's not just kindness.
There are many kinds of kindness, aren't there?
I feel that you are a person who is able to feel all of those various kinds of kindnesses.
I hope that you will continue to lead Tsubaki Factory.
I'm glad to hear that.
I will continue to do my best to lead Tsubaki Factory.
Haloste will continue after this.
Thank you for your hard work.
You have a sweet tooth for baking.
Don't let your heart fall out after spending time with Yaino's wine
Just friends
Two or three times I'm just tired
I'm sure that once upon a time
I'm sure she wasn't like this
Not like anyone.
I wasn't.
I had a good time, just fine.
I was the girl of my dreams... the girl of my dreams... the girl of my future.
Those good old days when hard work brought results
The days when I felt like I could make anything come true
Peace of mind... Peace of mind?
Yes.
Healing.
I'm not looking for luxury, I'm looking for simplicity.
I've been watching all these videos, and all I'm doing is watching.
It's just consuming my time.
I know I should just go to bed.
Love, love, love, love.
Love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love.
The kindness of people of people of people of people
Everything feels more difficult the older I get
Everything in my tears is crystal clear
Not a single cloud, pure vivacity
Everything inside me is transparent
of that time when I was a child
I'm still the same as I was when I was a little girl
I'm sleepy in the morning I'm sleepy on the night shift
I could sleep forever and ever I could sleep
But I'm still a friend. I'm still a friend.
I'm called away for some reason... and then I have to go out.
I'm sure I wasn't like this when I was a little girl.
I remember you smiling, yes, and you were good at it.
I remember that I could say what was on my mind, what was bothering me.
I was free to spoil you, to scream at you.
I trusted you with everything.
Memories, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes
I want to immerse myself in the world of a little bit of sechi
everything looks so good at the convenience store
Cakers, always buying the same thing
I know I should make it right every once in a while
Love love love love love love kind of love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love love
of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people of people
Everything, those of us who grow old just pretend not to notice
All transparent in their tears
Really honest and pure imitate
Everything inside me is transparent
When I was in love for the first time
As it was when I had my first love Still the same as when I had my first love
Yarabiru Pure Star
No more fantasy No more fantasy
Yaraviru Pure Star
Everything is getting older and pretending it won't unravel again
Everything in my tears is transparent
Really honest pure bye-bye
My friends, all transparent
When I was in love for the first time
Wow, wow, wow, wow
Just like when I had my first love
Ganba Ringo today!
This is Halo! Stay!
Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2024 Spring at Nippon Budokan on June 10 this month.
Come Everybody, Nene Maxora's graduation special “Ready Go Now” will be held at Nippon Budokan on June 10.
This time, I would like to talk to Kisora about a few things before her graduation.
So, first of all, how are you feeling now that there are only five days left until the graduation performance?
It's strange, isn't it?
Suddenly it's like...
I'm filled with a feeling of sadness when I think that the days I've taken for granted will suddenly disappear, but now I'm really looking forward to making the graduation performance a success with everyone, so I may be looking forward to it a bit.
I'm looking forward to it, but I'm not sure yet.
I guess I won't know until the day of the show, but I'm just looking forward to having fun.
We've been together since we formed the company, and we've been together for a long time.
I've been with Takamora for a long time now, and she really is like air.
It's just air, but it's like we're a family.
It's like we're family.
I don't have to worry about what I say because I can come in without any worries.
When you're in a group, you have to be careful.
But when I'm talking with Kisora, she's the only one I can use without really having to worry about anything.
I think that's why even when I'm having a hard time in the group, I feel more at ease because of Kisora.
It's like a place where I can feel safe and secure, like a place where my heart is at peace.
I feel like she's there for me.
I think she's the one who's been there for me.
Well, before Tsubaki Factory was formed and we made our debut, I used to commute to Tokyo from my home prefecture.
But I spent a lot of time with Ami-chan, and we stayed at a hotel together.
We spent a lot of time together in hotels and such.I'd like to know what it would be like if we were to break up.
I'm not sure if it's because I think the relationship between Ture and I was really brightly thinking about cinnamon or ganzi, so I wonder what it would be like to be separated from them. I think it's about diesex Beat I think it's weird that he's the defenders of the light, I think it's aesthetically pleasing, and I think it's been a long time since I've had a light like that, and I wonder what it is that makes people like that, like pepper and members, etc.
I feel that we are going our separate ways, but I think we still have dreams, so I hope we can shine in our respective places.
I hope we can shine in our respective places.
I'd like to talk about Kisora-chan, who I've seen and worked with closely.
I don't think she's the type to show off her hard work to others.
But in my mind, you're really good at your performance.
As I mentioned earlier, she has really established her idol image as Shinnuma Kisora.
It's really amazing to see it up close and personal.
Also, Kisora is very kind.
It's because of her pacifism.
Just by having her in the group, it makes us feel at ease.
She changes the atmosphere of the group.
I'm really glad that we could work together for so long.
Thank you very much.
So, you are the leader of Tsubaki Factory, and it was a little bit difficult for you...
But Riko Yamagishi was the leader for a long time.
It's because of Riko...
Yes, it was because of Riko.
I thought that the atmosphere of Tsubaki Factory was because of Riko's leadership.
I don't want to ruin that atmosphere.
I've been thinking that I want to make it easy for everyone to enjoy the activities as before.
But I also wondered what a leader does when it comes down to it.
I thought it was important to be myself.
I tried to be myself and work without being preoccupied.
I saw that Kouzubaki-chan became the leader from me.
But I really felt that she was more solid than ever.
I've been to a lot of events.
Yeah.
The events...
I'm thinking about how we're going to do the event, how we're going to connect with each other.
We're deciding how we want the formation to be.
But you take the initiative to tell us what you want to do.
He also takes good care of us.
I felt that the younger members rely on her a lot.
I am very glad that you are the leader of this group.
And now...
What is Tsubaki Factory Hello Project for Kisoda-chan?What is Tsubaki Factory Hello Project for Kisoda-chan?
Well, there are many things.
The first and foremost is that I admire them.
When I was little, I was influenced by watching Asuke Matsuura and Miki Fujimoto on TV.
I have loved Hello Project ever since then, so I applied for the audition.
I thought that admiration was the most important thing.
I still have feelings of respect and admiration for her.
I think that feeling will never change in the future.
Lastly, do you have a message for fans, viewers, and those attending the graduation lecture?
Yes, I do.
Thank you for all your support over the past 11 years.
Yes.
As Tsubaki Factory
I have met a lot of people through our many activities
and received warm love from the members and various staffs.
we have been able to continue our activities for almost 11 years.
I really don't think I would have been able to do this without your support
I don't think I would have been able to continue this long without your support.
I would not have been able to continue to do what I do without your support.
Your daily comments on my blog, your communication with me at individual events, etc.
Thanks to the warm words I received from everyone
I really received courage from you everyday.
I will do my best to repay your courage, energy and love on the day of the graduation lecture.
I will do my best to repay the courage, energy, and love you have given me on the day of my graduation lecture.
I would like to ask for your support for Kisra Ninja until the end.
So I hope you will watch over me until the end.
Thank you very much.
One more last song.
We are now
We're here now.
Yes!
Spread the wings of your dreams
Blake! I'm Blake!
I'll ask you what you want.
I'm gonna ask you what you want, and you're gonna tell me about Mexico.
I'll tell you what I don't know, and you'll tell me what you do.If you start with something you don't know or something you don't know...
Information rocks!
This is what we're going to do
We're still dreaming
We're still in the middle of a dream
Oh, okay, whatever you say
The opportunity's there
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yes!
Yes! Your life's still here
Oh, you may mourn and pine
Yes! Still open the wings of your dreams
devi
devi tee
Spirit
I'm sorry, when I wanted it
It felt like that time
All in pieces, all in pieces, all in disarray, all in disarray, all in disarray.
It's like we're all in this together
Love and goodbye
I'll never forget the smile
In the moonlight, the song goes beyond me
I'll go on and on and on
In the moonlight, spread your love's wings
On you
I'll shout it right here, right now
Foo!
Ho ول! Ho funktioniert.
Geras is a drum!
Beyond me
I'll go on and on and on
I'll go on
Yeah Ilma la la la la I
Spread your wings
I'll find you
Oh, Kimi, you're screaming now
Break, break, break, break yourself down
Wow, wow, wowWow Wow Wow
Such a ravishing
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
If you get your mind off it
Wow Wow Wow
Such Rabbi Forting
Rabbi forting
This ned side I can grow
oh oh oh everyone's Revolving Girls
oh oh oh oh oh
Let's walk out
oh oh oh Everybody's Revolving Girls
Revolving Girls
I can't jump jump jump
Woo
Thank you
We're almost there
Fight!
This is Halo! Sta. of Tsubaki Factory and Ami Tanimoto.
It's almost time to say goodbye.
I was the last MC this time, but I felt relieved to be able to work with Ami.
I also felt nostalgic while doing the recording.
I was glad to be with Ami at the end.
I'm so glad that I was able to MC with Kisora for the last time at Halo! I'm also very happy that I was able to MC with Kisora for the last time.
I was also very sad to hear that Kisora was graduating.
Whenever I do something with you or talk with you, it's always difficult for me to finish.
But I think we were able to do our best until the end today.
I'm glad.
I'm glad we were able to make it to the end today.
Here is an announcement.
Tsubaki Factory's 12th single will be released on August 28th!
It's a triple A-side single including a new song, Baby Spider: Youth Exobyte!
This will be Kisora-chan's last single, so please pay attention to it!
And Tsubaki Factory Concert Tour 2024 Spring
Kamo Everybody Rinnu Makisura Graduation Special
Lady Go!Ready Go!
will be held at the Nippon Budokan on June 10!
I was also involved in the set list for this show.
I am confident that this will be an enjoyable performance.
I hope that many of you will come.
And I would like to share with you my photo book of Rinnuma Kisra.
Kisla is now on sale!
You'll be able to see a lot of different Kisora-chan in it, so please get it!
And on June 29th.
I will be performing at Alive Sendai Vol. 2!
It will be a live performance by Ibinari Tohoku Mishima Tsuman, so please look forward to it!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
Every week, a video will appear on the channel every few days, so please look forward to it!
We hope you enjoy it!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday.
Please give us a high rating, leave a comment, and subscribe to our channel!
This time we have Makisora Oshino and Ami Tanimoto from Tsubaki Factory.
and Ami Tanimoto of Tsubaki Factory.
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!